https://www.allflesh.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Your privacy is important to us. It is All Flesh’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://www.allflesh.com, and other sites we own and operate.
We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.
We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.
You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.
Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.
This policy is effective as of 11 March 2020.
Search for:
ALL FLESH MUST BE EATEN March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
Worlds of the Dead: A Collection of Dead Worlds March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
Zombie Smack Down Source Book March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
Dungeons and Zombies March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
All Tomorrow’s Zombies March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
THE BOOK OF MORE FLESH Anthology Novel March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
A Fistfull of Zombies Source Book March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
One of the Living: Player’s Handbook March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
ALL FLESH MUST BE EATEN Main Rule Book March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
Pulp Zombies Source Book March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
Characters March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
Enter the Zombie Source Book March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
One of the Living: Player’s Handbook March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
A Fistfull of Zombies Source Book March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
THE BOOK OF MORE FLESH Anthology Novel March 11, 2020March 11, 2020
No comments found.
No tags created.
Categories
All Flesh
Dead Worlds
Zombies
Powered by WordPress and Bam.
